Charlie Lowe

Games Development Student

Contact

charlielowe04@gmail.com 07805 711251 https://charlielowe.github.io/ Norwich, UK

Skills

- Unreal Engine
- C++
- Unity
- C#
- Godot
- Python
- Time management
- Team work
- Problem Solving
- Leadership

Specialisms

- Gameplay mechanics
- Game design
- Bug fixing

Education

Norwich University of the Arts BSc Games Development

September 2023 - Present, NORWICH

About Me

I am an aspiring game programmer specialising in C++ within Unreal Engine 5. I enjoy making unique indie games that focus on new and interesting gameplay mechanics. I've been learning how to code for over 7 years and have participated in an array of game jams, both solo and as a team.

Projects

Global Game Jam

December 2024 - Programmer

- Developed gameplay features
- Fixed bugs and optimised code
- Collaborated with fellow developers and other teams
- Worked effectively within a deadline

Devtober

December 2024 - Team Leader/Programmer

- Managed team, assigning roles and deadlines
- Brainstormed game ideas
- Created systems for dialogue and deck building
- Fixed bugs and optimised code

Employment

Student Ambassador - Norwich University of the Arts

September 2023 - Present

- Leading campus tours for groups of prospective students
- Providing support at open days
- Promoted the university and my course
- Helped with running events for the games industry, such as the UKIE Women in Games event

I.T. Support Engineer - The Access Group

May 2021 - March 2023

- Managed IT systems and provided technical support at a leading law firm.
- Collaborated with colleagues from a range of teams
- Wrote scripts to automate processes
- Communicated with clients on the phone, over emails, and face to face on a daily basis.